NICK WHISLER

github.com/nwhisler in linkedin.com/in/nwhisler/

♥ Lynchburg, VA 24502

434 401 4191

■ nwhisl@gmail.com

Summary Of Qualifications

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C++, C, Assembly Language, SQL, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript Operating Systems: Windows, Linux (Ubuntu)

Knowledge of data and discrete structures, search, sorting, and encryption algorithms, data wrangling, Bayesian (A/B testing), supervised, unsupervised, and deep machine learning, Keras, TensorFlow, Theano, and software testing.

Customer experience, service, and satisfaction.

EDUCATION —

Bachelor of Science:

Computer Science
Jan. 2021 – May 2023

Colorado State University

Fort Collins, CO GPA: 3.47 Honor Society

Bachelor of Science:

Physics

Jan. 2015 – Dec. 2016 Radford University Radford, VA GPA: 3.45

Sigma Pi Sigma:

Physics National Honor Society

Bootcamp Certification: Machine Learning and

Engineering Career Track

Springboard

Feb 2019 – Jul 2019 San Francisco, CA

EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2021 – May 2021 Cashier • McDonald's

Aug. 2019 - Nov. 2019

Sales and Stock Associate • The Home Depot

Feb. 2019 – May 2019 Server • Monte Carlo

Feb. 2018 - May 2018

Customer Service Representative • Startek

May 2017 – Jul. 2017

Customer Service Representative • Startek

Aug. 2015 – Dec. 2015

Teaching Assistant • Radford University

Aug. 2015 – Dec. 2015 Mentor • Radford University

Jun. 2015 - Aug. 2015

Work Study • Radford University

KEY SKILLS -

Software

Data Science
Machine Learning

Statistics

Volunteering

Intrepid USA Healthcare Services

Jun. 2015 - Aug. 2015

Children's Miracle Network Jan. 2004 – Jan. 2011